[{"question": " hey!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " who wants french toast?", "answer": " oh, i&#146;ll have some!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " good, me too.  eggs and milk are in the fridge. thanks.", "answer": "  oww!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " what&#146;s the matter honey?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know, my hand feels weird. i guess it&#146;s because, i&#146;m engaged!  how long before it starts getting annoying?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " it starts?", "answer": " yeah, so let&#146;s get started on the wedding plans!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": "  already?!", "answer": " yeah, we got a lot to do! we gotta think about the flowers, the caterers, the music&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " oh, i got some thoughts on that.", "answer": " oh wait chandler, too many cooks&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " take from me, as the groom all you have to do is show up and try to say the right name.", "answer": "  okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " what in god&#146;s name is that?!", "answer": " oh my god, the wedding book?! i haven&#146;t seen that since the forth grade!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " this baby has got everything. take y&#146;know, locations for instance.  first, organized alphabetically, then geographically, then by square footage.", "answer": " that is so smart!  break it off. break it off now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " hey! ross!", "answer": " phoebe, oh my god! wh-wh-what are you doing here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " i need to talk to you, it&#146;s pretty urgent. it&#146;s about monica and chandler.", "answer": " oh my god! of course, of course.  umm, would you please excuse me for a moment? umm, do you know each other&#146;s hometowns? why don&#146;t you&#133;   wh-what&#146;s going on?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " well, umm, not much. but, i was just thinking that since those guys just got engaged that maybe it would be nice if they had some privacy, y&#146;know? so, could i just move in with you for a couple days?", "answer": " umm, okay, yeah, sure. but wh-what&#146;s wrong with monica and chandler?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " nothing&#151;why?!", "answer": " phoebe, you said it was urgent!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " oh yeah it is! i&#146;m going to the movies and it starts in like five minutes.", "answer": " do you realize i have a classroom full of students?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " all right, so i haven&#146;t cleared the budget with my parents yet, but tell me how this is for music.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " all right umm, a string quartet for the procession.", "answer": " aw.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " a jazz trio for cocktails. the bay city rollers for dancing. wait, that was from my sixth grade wedding.", "answer": " well, you couldn&#146;t get them anyway. ian doesn&#146;t plan anymore and derrick&#133;  and derrick is a name i shouldn&#146;t know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": "  hey mon, do you have another pillow?  y&#146;know, something a little snugglyer?", "answer": " why are you napping over here instead of over at your place?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " well, the duck&#133;", "answer": " what?! the duck?! what the hell did the damn duck do now?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " uh, well he did not get sick somewhere in there and it was immediately found and properly cleaned up!", "answer": " now, do i get to look at this book or is it just for people who are actually involved in the wedding?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " of course you can look at it! yeah, i want your opinion too!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " here you go! what do you think about centerpieces?", "answer": " centerpieces!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " definitely roses.  well, i just think they&#146;re a little more weddingy.  but lilies are the clear choice.", "answer": " oh my god! it&#146;s like one mind.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " uh-huh!", "answer": "  guys! guys!! you gotta let me nap! ugh, i&#146;m gonna get cranky!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " joey, there is a perfectly good couch across the hall!", "answer": " yes it is perfectly good, and it is not one of the places the duck got sick!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " all right, i&#146;m gonna go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " now joey, what did the duck do?!", "answer": " i don&#146;t know! but he did not eat your face cream!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " uh, phoebe&#133;", "answer": " oh ross, hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " phoebe, what are you doing?", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry, i&#146;m with a client right now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " phoebe!", "answer": " okay, let&#146;s talk outside.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " phoebe, you can&#146;t massage people in my apartment!", "answer": " what&#146;s the big deal? i did it at monica and chandler&#146;s!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " and they knew about it?", "answer": "  okay, well ross, what is this really about?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " look, this is my home and i want to be able to come and go whenever i want!", "answer": " okay, i will find someplace else to do the rest of my appointments. i just don&#146;t know what the big deal is!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " hey joey, what &#145;cha doing?", "answer": " sweepin&#146;. why? turn you on?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " huh. what if i was sweeping a chimney?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " joey,  where did you learn that word?", "answer": " where do you think,  zelda?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": "  you found my book?!", "answer": " yeah i did!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " joey, what-what are you doing going into my bedroom?!", "answer": " okay, look i&#146;m sorry, i went in there to take a nap and i know i shouldn&#146;t have, but you got porn!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " hello.", "answer": " hi, is uh phoebe here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " uh no-no, she-she&#146;s out for the night.", "answer": " ohh great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " can i, can i help you with something?", "answer": " well, i don&#146;t know. are you a masseur?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": "  yes i am.", "answer": " great!  dad!  thank you so much, i&#146;ll be back to pick him up in an hour.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " so chandler, you&#146;re parents must&#146;ve been thrilled when you told them you were engaged.", "answer": " oh yeah, i should probably call them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " i remember when we first got engaged.", "answer": " oh, i don&#146;t think i ever heard that story.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " oh dad, really you don&#146;t need to&#133;", "answer": "  well, i&#146;d gotten judy pregnant. i still don&#146;t know that happened.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": "  you don&#146;t know how that happened?! your dog thought my diaphragm was a chew toy!", "answer": " what a sweet story.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " well, at least you&#146;re not hearing it for the first time at your fifth grade halloween party.", "answer": " what?! they wanted a scary story!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " anyway, we&#146;re really excited about our wedding plans, and well i guess pretty soon we&#146;ll be making a big withdrawal from the monica wedding fund.  what?", "answer": " you tell her jack, i can&#146;t do it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " what happened? you still have the monica wedding fund don&#146;t you?", "answer": " we have it. only now, we call it the beach house. commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " i don&#146;t believe you spent my wedding fund on the beach house!", "answer": " we&#146;re sorry honey, but we just assumed if you got married after you turned 30 you&#146;d pay for it yourself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " you bought the beach house when i was 23!", "answer": " which means you had seven years of beach fun and you can&#146;t put a price on that sweetie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " we really do feel bad about this though.", "answer": " we started saving again when you were dating richard and then that went to hell, so we redid the kitchen.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " what about when i started dating chandler?", "answer": " well it was chandler! we didn&#146;t think he&#146;d ever propose!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " i can&#146;t believe it! that there is no money for my wedding?!", "answer": " we might still have some money, if your father didn&#146;t think it was a good idea to sell ice over the internet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " it seemed like such a simple idea.", "answer": " stupid jack, the word is stupid.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " i can&#146;t believe this. do you think that your parents could help pay for it?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know, my mother spent most of her money on her fourth wedding. she&#146;s saving the rest for her divorce. and any extra cash my father has he saves for his yearly trips to  dollywood.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " well what happened at dinner?", "answer": " my parents spent the money for our wedding!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": "  my god! what did you order?!", "answer": " wait, but there&#146;s no money! well this is terrible! you guys are gonna have to get married in like a, rec. center!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " honey, it&#146;s gonna be okay.", "answer": " no! no it&#146;s not! it&#146;s not gonna be okay! it sucks! no swing band! no lilies!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " look, it really is gonna be okay. the important thing is that we love each other and that we&#146;re gonna get married.", "answer": " do you even understand what off the rack means?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " look, why don&#146;t you just pay for it yourself?", "answer": " how? i don&#146;t have any money.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " well, i have some.", "answer": " how much?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " whoa!!! are you kidding me?!", "answer": " well what?! how-how much is it?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " it&#146;s enough for wedding scenario eight.", "answer": " ohh!  really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": "  how great are you, you little saver?! i mean, the-the amount you have is exactly the budget of my dream wedding!", "answer": "  ohh, you guys are so made for each other.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " well, you&#146;re not suggesting that we spend all of the money on the wedding? rachel and monica: ah, yeah!", "answer": " well, come on, i&#146;ve been saving this money for six years and i kinda had some of it earmarked for the future, not just for a party.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": "  wow!  hello, mr. chandler.", "answer": " this is the most special day of our lives.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " no, i realize that honey, but i&#146;m not gonna spend all of the money on one party.", "answer": " honey, umm i-i love you,  but umm, if you call our wedding a party one more time, you may not get invited. okay?  listen, we could always earn more money, okay? but uh, we&#146;re only gonna get married once.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " look, i understand, but i have to put my foot down. okay? the answer is no.", "answer": " you-you&#146;re gonna have to put your foot down?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " yes, i am!", "answer": " wow, money and a firm hand. finally a chandler i can get on board with.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " hey rach.", "answer": "  joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " hey rach, do you smell smoke?", "answer": " uh-huh, i get it, smoke, chimney, chimney sweep, very funny, ha-ha.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " no-no-no, i&#146;m serious. you don&#146;t smell it? something&#146;s on fire.", "answer": " well no, i don&#146;t smell anything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " oh, y&#146;know what? it&#146;s probably just your burnin&#146; loins.", "answer": "  hey, what are you guys, what are you guys talking about?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " nothing!", "answer": "  damn, this coffee&#146;s cold! hey rach, do you mind if i heat this up on your loins?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " y&#146;know, i can not believe you told him, joey!", "answer": " so i guess you bought that book after we broke up huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": "  oh yeah, yeah? well uh, when we were going out, i read tons of porno magazines!   &#145;sup?", "answer": "  ross! how could you do that to an old man?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": "  excuse me ladies.  i&#146;m sorry?", "answer": " my massage client, arthur? his daughter called and said that some guy that worked for me gave him a really weird massage this afternoon.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": "  i gave him an extremely professional massage!", "answer": " he said you poked at him with wooden spoons.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " okay, so it wasn&#146;t uh, a traditional massage. but i did give him accu-pressure with a pair of chopsticks. and, and i gently exfoliated him with, with a mop.", "answer": " well, he&#146;s never coming back! okay? you just cost me eight dollars a week!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " hey, y&#146;know what? this is your fault! you&#146;re the one that didn&#146;t move his-his appointment.", "answer": " oh, it&#146;s my fault?! you didn&#146;t have to massage him! you could&#146;ve sent him away! you could&#146;ve not rolled tonka trucks up and down his back!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " he said he liked that!! oh you&#146;re right, you&#146;re right. i&#146;m sorry.", "answer": " dude, what are you massaging an old man for?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " his daughter was hot.", "answer": " gotcha.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " listen umm, i&#146;ve been thinking, it&#146;s not fair for me to ask you to spend all of your money on our wedding. i mean, you work, you work really hard for that.", "answer": " ehh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " eh, you work for that.", "answer": " look, i thought about it too, and i&#146;m sorry. i think we should spend all of the money on the wedding.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " you do?!", "answer": " yeah, i&#146;m putting my foot down. yeah look, when i proposed i told you that i would do anything to make you happy, and if having the perfect wedding makes you happy then, then that&#146;s what we&#146;re gonna do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " oh, you&#146;re so sweet.  oh, but wait, what about our, what about the future and stuff?", "answer": " eh, forget about the future and stuff! so we only have two kids, y&#146;know? we&#146;ll pick our favorite and that one will get to go to college.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " you thought about that?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " how many kids were we gonna have?", "answer": " uh, four, a boy, twin girls and another boy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " what else did you think about?", "answer": " well, stuff like where&#146;d we live, y&#146;know? like a small place outside the city, where our kids could learn to ride their bikes and stuff. y&#146;know, we could have a cat that had a bell on it&#146;s collar and we could hear it every time it ran through the little kitty door. of course, we&#146;d have an apartment over the garage where joey could grow old.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": "  y&#146;know what? i-i don&#146;t want a big, fancy wedding.", "answer": " sure you do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " no, i want everything you just said. i want a marriage.", "answer": " you sure?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " uh-hmm.", "answer": " i love you so much.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " i love you.  hey listen umm, when, when you were talkin&#146; about our future you said cat, but you meant dog right.", "answer": " oh yeah, totally!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " hello, zelda.", "answer": " who are you supposed to be?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " the vicar!", "answer": " do you even know what a vicar is?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " like a goalie, right?", "answer": "  yeah. look joey, it&#146;s enough all right?! you keep making these stupid jokes and this sleazy innuendoes and it&#146;s&#151;i&#146;m not&#151;it&#146;s just not funny anymore!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " all right! y&#146;know what? that&#146;s it! you wanna do it?! let&#146;s do it!", "answer": " huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": "  that&#146;s right, i wanna do it with you! i&#146;ve been trying to fight it, but you just said all the right things.", "answer": "  i-i-i-i did?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": "  yeah! ohh, i&#146;ve been waitin&#146; so long to get on that body!", "answer": " this body?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " yeah that&#146;s right! come on joey; sex me up!", "answer": " hey-hey, you&#146;re startin&#146; to sound like the butcher&#146;s wife there in-in chapter seven.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}]